Jets and off here we GO.
This is where the blue area fine is regulated.
Now I'll have to go by bus because the Chevette isn't working.
Bro.
Calm down bus
I had 3 neighborhoods to do and I won't be able to get there bro I'm going to
have to cancel about 20 little boxes more OR less because of this event.
That's what happened with Chevette.
Show you everywhere here so I can deliver today.
Since the car broke half of it,
I won't give it up.
I'll have to sell on the street so I don't lose that stock.
Is it on?
Let's go to this
make a delivery to Brunão and the crowd here.
Wanting the rest of their day.
You'll want something.
Damn let me give the change.
That's what the fuck,
there's no dog hunting with a cat,
you can't stand still.
Lamenting there didn't work out.
Use the tools you have and march through progress.
Oh I'll have to walk six blocks.
Screw.
If bro customer has nothing to do with it.
He paid.
Good morning people maintenance.
I came here to fix your day,
girl I'm from the Brigadier's workshop.
Bye girls,
everything good for you was enough.
Our face is going a lot.
is heavy.
Oh my chills in hand here
And that.
Honestly I have no idea what will happen in the next few days.
If this all doesn't happen and this series ends.
At least I tried.
Sacou mano?
The goal here is always to motivate you to go after what you want.
Sometimes it can work,
sometimes it can go wrong.
It's part of life and that's worth it.